I would like to talk now about the meaning of a bedroom and the purpose of the bedroom.
So the meaning of a bedroom is that bedroom represents our inner self.
And when I go to people's homes and I see that public spaces downstairs are very nice and neat and beautiful and designed and when I go to the bedroom, their bedroom and see that it is cluttered, it is dark, it is not attended.
So it tells me something about the person.
It tells me that they probably are not confident enough in themselves.
Or perhaps they do not take good care of themselves.
Or perhaps they do not take good care of their relationship.
So their purpose of the bedroom is to have a good night sleep of course.
It's rest, rejuvenation.
And another purpose is to make love, to have relationship, to honor your relationship in a bedroom.